// Holds the data for the app in the form of an array of objects
const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'Which river serperates OR from WA?',
    answers: ['Willamete River', 'Glenn Jackson River', 'Columbia River', 'Hood River'],
    correctAnswer: 'Columbia River',
  },

  {
    question: 'The Pittock Mansion overlooks which city?',
    answers: ['Vancouver', 'Portland', 'Milwaukie', 'Happy Valley'],
    correctAnswer: 'Portland',
  },

  {
    question: 'What company sponsers the orange bikes?',
    answers: ['Addidas', 'Nike', 'Intel', 'Columbia Sports Wear'],
    correctAnswer: 'Nike',
  },

  {
    question: 'What fountain is located at water front park?',
    answers: ['Water Front Fountains', 'Salmon Street Springs', 'Lovejoy Fountain', 'The Dreamer'],
    correctAnswer: 'Salmon Street Springs',
  },

  {
    question: 'What is the closest snow-capped mountain to Portland?',
    answers: ['Mt Saint Helens', 'Mount Hood', 'Mount Rainer', 'Mount Adams'],
    correctAnswer: 'Mount Hood',
  },

  {
    question: 'How high is Mt Hood?',
    answers: ['5,000 Ft', '8,000 Ft', '11,000 Ft', '13,000 Ft'],
    correctAnswer: '11,000 Ft',
  },

  {
    question: 'What is the name of the inactive volcano on the east end of Portland?',
    answers: ['Mt Hood', 'Mt Saint Helens', 'Mount Tabor', 'Mount Blanc'],
    correctAnswer: 'Mount Tabor',
  },

  {
    question: 'The streets in the northwest section of Portland are organized how?',
    answers: ['Alphabetically', 'Numerically', 'By state names', 'By Alpaha Numerically'],
    correctAnswer: 'Alphabetically',
  },

  {
    question: 'Which famous television show uses several street names from Portland?',
    answers: ['Family Guy', 'Friends', 'The Simpsons', 'American Dad'],
    correctAnswer: 'The Simpsons',
  },

  {
    question: 'Approximately how many blocks in northwest Portland fit into one mile?',
    answers: ['10', '20', '25', '30'],
    correctAnswer: '20',
  }
];